Guide to the Doris Duke Photograph Collection, 1870-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General, 1909-2001 and undated
  - Black and white portraits of Joey Castro. Portraits include headshots in connection with Clover Records, some negatives and contact sheets, 1965 (3 of 3) (Box 47, Folder PHGEN014)
  - Black and white photographs of Julia Ward Howe bust on loan to The Redwood Library from Doris Duke. Bust currently resides at the Samuel Whitehorne House in Newport, RI, 1968 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN015)
  - Black and white photographs of Alec Cunningham-Reid, 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN016)
  - Black and white photograph or headshot of Joey Castro, 1950-1955 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN017)
  - Sepia portrait of James Cromwell, 1935-1940 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN018)
  - Black and white photograph of Porfirio Rubirosa, standing with polo stick and horse. Reverse of photo reads, "G. Lover", 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN020)
  - Color photos of Joey Castro. Photos were enclosed in a letter to Doris Duke April 1961, 1961 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN021)
  - Black and white photographs sent to Doris Duke from Alec Cunningham-Reid. One photo is of Capt. Reid and the other is of his house. The woman in this shot is unidentified, 1941 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN022)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting a golf outing with Porfirio Rubirosa, 1947-1950 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN023)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs involving Porfirio Rubirosa, a plane, boat, and beach activities, 1947-1950 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN024)
  - Black and white photograph, wallet-size, of Walker P. Inman Jr., circa 1965 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN025)
  - Sepia photograph of Porfirio Rubirosa, on horse, shaking hands with unidentified woman, 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN026)
  - Black and white photograph of Robert Banks, composer. Photograph carries inscription, "To Doris Duke With Gratitude Robert Banks", 1960-1965 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN027)
  - Sepia photograph of Leta Morris, Doris Duke's childhood friend. Inscription reads, "To Doris with Lots of Love from Leta. Xmas 1927." (Box 47, Folder PHGEN028)
  - Black and white photographs of Leta MacBean, 1940-1945 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN029)
  - Color and Black and white photographs of Louis Bromfield in relation to his radio announcements for Pontiac. Photos sent to Miss Duke from "Bill", 1955-1956 (Box 47, Folder PHGEN030)
  - Reproduction of photograph of Amir Fuaz, "The War-Lord of the Ruala, Amir Fuaz", undated (Box 48, Folder PHGEN004)
  - Portraits of actress Marlene Dietrich, Paramount Pictures, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 48, Folder PHGEN005)
  - Portraits of Alec Cunningham-Reid, circa 1940s (Box 48, Folder PHGEN006)
  - Portrait of Franklin D. Roosevelt. Includes inscription "To Jimmy and Doris Cromwell from their friend Franklin D. Roosevelt", circa 1930s (Box 48, Folder PHGEN007)
  - Portraits of Alec Cunningham-Reid smoking cigar, circa 1940s (Box 48, Folder PHGEN008)
  - Black and white photograph of Cobina Wright, columnist with the LA Herald & Express. Photo shows Cobina sitting at her piano and holding poodle. Inscribed to Doris Duke, 1952 (Box 48, Folder PHGEN019)
  - Black and white photograph of Bill Robinson, inscribed to Doris Duke, 1937 (Box 48, Folder PHGEN109)
  - Black and white photograph of a group of military officers taken at Northwestern University, circa 1940s (Box 48, Folder PHGEN110)
  - Color photographs of the interior and exterior of the restored railway car, 'Doris', undated (Box 48, Folder PHGEN111)
  - Reproduction of photograph of Franklin D Roosevelt, undated (Box 48, Folder PHGEN112)
  - Selection of ektachromes documenting "Mom's Visit to NY and Farm I II III". Woman is Joey Castro's mother, 1955-1960 (Box 49, Folder PHGEN031)
  - Black and white photograph of Walker Inman Jr. taken at the Royal Hawaiian Hotel, HI, 1955 (Box 49, Folder PHGEN032)
  - Black and white photograph of Johnny Gomez. Photo is inscribed, circa 1937 (Box 49, Folder PHGEN033)
  - Black and white portrait, young woman, possibly Dorothy Mahana, Miss Duke's childhood friend, circa 1920 (Box 49, Folder PHGEN034)
  - Color photographs of objects, located in Shangri La, sent to NJ for final destination to Walker P. Inman Jr. WPI received objects as part of the settlement of Doris Duke's will. Pieces located at Shangri La, Living Room (4551/4564) on 4/28/99, 2001 (Box 49, Folder PHGEN035)
  - Color photographs of jade pieces. Photos may have been sent to Doris Duke before purchase to choose from. Descriptive information marked on reverse. Some are labeled Punnett Galleries, circa 1980 (Box 49, Folder PHGEN037)
  - Black and white photographs of Porfirio Rubirosa with black dog. Cibao La Pampa was the name of his polo team, 1947-1950 (Box 49, Folder PHGEN038)
  - The Chinese Bedroom showing pieces from the suite, now dispersed, circa early 1900s (reproduction on foam core) (Box 50, Folder PHGEN039)
  - Silhouette of Leta McDonald inscribed to Doris Duke, 1923 (Box 50, Folder PHGEN040)
  - Black and white stereoscopic images manufactured by the Keystone Stereoscopic Service. Most likely used by Doris Duke to help strengthen her vision, circa 1930s (1 of 2) (Box 50, Folder PHGEN041)
  - Black and white stereoscopic images manufactured by the Keystone Stereoscopic Service. Most likely used by Doris Duke to help strengthen her vision, circa 1930s (2 of 2) (Box 50, Folder PHGEN042)
  - Doris Duke in Bangkok on her honeymoon in 1935 (reproduction on foam core) (Box 50, Folder PHGEN043)
  - Doris Duke in Bombay, India on her honeymoon in 1935 (reproduction on foam core) (Box 50, Folder PHGEN044)
  - Doris Duke and James Cromwell at their estate, Shangri La, 1939 (reproduction on foam core) (Box 50, Folder PHGEN045)
  - Black and white photographs of Katherine Dunham, circa 1940s (Box 50, Folder PHGEN046)
  - Black and white studio shot of Alec Cunningham-Reid, also includes two photographs of Alec Cunningham-Reid with son, circa 1940s (Box 50, Folder PHGEN047)
  - Black and white photographs of Baker's Ranch, Reno, NV, 1940-1945 (Box 50, Folder PHGEN048)
  - Black and white photographs of pet dogs by Ernie Mack, Reno, NV, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 50, Folder PHGEN049)
  - Doris Duke working with a member of the U.S. Seamens Service in New Orleans, Louisiana, 1944 (reproduction on foam core) (Box 50, Folder PHGEN050)
  - Black and white photographs of a woman named Ginger. All photographs are inscribed to "Lahi Lahi", Doris Duke's nickname, 1949 (Box 50, Folder PHGEN051)
  - Color photographs and slides of Charles Asfar [?] and other unknown individuals, Damascus, Syria[?], circa 1950s (Box 50, Folder PHGEN052)
  - Photographs and negatives of various unidentified men, 1950s-1980s (Box 50, Folder PHGEN053)
  - A portrait of Doris Duke in 1953. Courtesy of Wallace Seawell (reproduction on foam core) (Box 51, Folder PHGEN054)
  - Sri Daya Mata of the Self Realization Fellowship, 1959 and undated (Box 51, Folder PHGEN055)
  - Photographs from the UCLA Conference on the "Indian Project" (probably the American Indian History Project), circa 1960s (Box 51, Folder PHGEN056)
  - A view of the Music Room at Rough Point, 1960s (reproduction on foam core) (Box 51, Folder PHGEN057)
  - Color negatives of studio shots of Kitty White, Clover Records artist, circa 1960s (Box 51, Folder PHGEN058)
  - Black and white photographs of Jackie Kennedy visiting New York University, 1962 Oct 18 (Box 51, Folder PHGEN059)
  - Photographs of various unknown locations, 1962 and undated (Box 51, Folder PHGEN060)
  - Photographs, Christmas with Kina, Jumata, Nona, Rampa, possibly in Hawaii at Shangri La, 1964 (Box 51, Folder PHGEN061)
  - Doris Duke on visit to India in 1966 (reproduction on foam core) (Box 51, Folder PHGEN062)
  - Photographs, slides and correspondence of Clover Records artist Terry Edwads, circa 1966 (Box 51, Folder PHGEN063)
  - Photographs of a trip to Nepal, India, 1968 (Box 51, Folder PHGEN064)
  - Photograph of Martha Graham sent to Doris Duke from Ron Protas, 1969 (Box 51, Folder PHGEN065)
  - Photographs and slides of various unidentified women, 1976 and undated (Box 51, Folder PHGEN066)
  - Color photographs of various doors at Duke Farms, circa 1978 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN067)
  - Photographs, pets, Myrna and her puppies, 1978 Aug 15, presumably from Miss Duke's office (Box 52, Folder PHGEN068)
  - Photographs of Charleston House, 1981 Apr 29 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN069)
  - Photographs, Trail Blazers Camp, Port Jervis, NY, 1983 Oct 12 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN070)
  - Photographs at NRF property, 1984 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN071)
  - Tourist booklet and color photographs of Russia or Romania, circa 1984 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN072)
  - Photographs of lantern sent to Doris Duke at Duke Farms from Johnny Gomez, 1984 Jan 18 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN073)
  - Photographs of Cat, cow, Dogs, 1987 and undated (Box 52, Folder PHGEN074)
  - Color photographs of various rugs at Duke Farms (?) in need of repair 1989 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN075)
  - Color photograph of Imelda Marcos inscribed to Doris Duke and Chandi Heffner, 1990 Jun 17 (Box 52, Folder PHGEN076)
  - Black and white photograph of Roseanna Todd, given o Joan Spero, 1998 Jun (Box 52, Folder PHGEN077)
  - Cover of Christie's Auction of the Doris Duke Collection, sold to benefit the Doris Duke Charitable foundation, 2004 Jun (mounted on foam core) (Box 52, Folder PHGEN078)
  - Black and white and color photographs of dogs at various estates, undated (Box 52, Folder PHGEN079)
  - Black and white photos - Chinese Silver Bronze Sacrificial Vessel, Shang Dynasty, compliments of Mr. Alfred Salmony, undated (Box 52, Folder PHGEN080)
  - Black and white photographs of circular pool inside a building, in an envelope marked "hold pictures for Miss Duke", undated (Box 52, Folder PHGEN081)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown buildings and gardens, undated (Box 52, Folder PHGEN082)
  - Black and white photographs (faded) possibly of Doris Duke's bed, undated (Box 52, Folder PHGEN083)
  - Black and white photographs of Norma Shearer and Peggy Lee, both inscribed to Doris Duke, undated (Box 52, Folder PHGEN084)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown men, presumably acquaintances or friends of Doris Duke, undated (1 of 2) (Box 52, Folder PHGEN085)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown men, presumably acquaintances or friends of Doris Duke, undated (2 of 2) (Box 52, Folder PHGEN086)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown women and children, presumably acquaintances or friends of Doris Duke, undated (1 of 3) (Box 53, Folder PHGEN087)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown women and children, presumably acquaintances or friends of Doris Duke, undated (2 of 3) (Box 53, Folder PHGEN088)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown women and children, presumably acquaintances or friends of Doris Duke, undated (3 of 3) (Box 53, Folder PHGEN089)
  - Duke Farms Main Residence, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 53, Folder PHGEN090)
  - Miscellaneous black and white, color photographs of unknown people, unknown locations, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN091)
  - Miscellaneous black and white negatives, includes Shangri La, Doris Duke, and unknown people and locations, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN092)
  - Miscellaneous images presumably of the Middle East, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN093)
  - Photograph of coffee serving set, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 53, Folder PHGEN094)
  - Photographs of an Indian man, Iris Paris Studio, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN095)
  - Photograph of Japanese Garden, Duke Farms (?), undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 53, Folder PHGEN096)
  - Photograph of Matha Graham by Ron Protas, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN097)
  - Photographs of serving dishes of Rosanna Todd, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN098)
  - Photograph of silverware in Butlers Pantry, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 53, Folder PHGEN099)
  - Photographs and slides from Shalammar Gardens, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN100)
  - Photographs of unidentified building, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN101)
  - Photographs of unknown people, probably Doris Duke's acquaintances, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN102)
  - Photographs of several unknown locations, undated (Box 53, Folder PHGEN103)
  - Black and white photographs of USS Atlanta, inscribed by Captain SP Jenkins, circa 1940s (Box 54, Folder PHGEN113)
  - Black and white photographs of Walker Inman Jr as a little boy, circa 1950s (Box 54, Folder PHGEN114)
  - Black and white photographs of Walker Inman Jr as a young man, circa 1960s (Box 54, Folder PHGEN115)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown men, two are inscribed to Doris Duke, undated (1 of 2) (Box 54, Folder PHGEN116)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown men, two are inscribed to Doris Duke, undated (2 of 2) (Box 54, Folder PHGEN116)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown women and children, undated (1 of 2) (Box 54, Folder PHGEN118)
  - Black and white photographs of unknown women and children, undated (2 of 2) (Box 54, Folder PHGEN118)
  - Black and white photograph of Walker Inman Jr.'s House, undated (Box 54, Folder PHGEN120)
  - Reproductions of various artworks, undated (Box 54, Folder PHGEN121)
  - Portrait of unknown man, 1909 (Box 55, Folder PHGEN122)
  - Pet dogs, undated (1 of 2) (Box 55, Folder PHGEN123)
  - Pet dogs, undated (2 of 2) (Box 55, Folder PHGEN123)
  - Ocean view shot of Shangri La, spelled "Shangriila", 1938 Sep 14 (Box 56, Folder PHGEN125)
  - Aerials of Shangri La and Diamond Head, circa 1950s (Box 56, Folder PHGEN126)
  - A view of Duke Farms, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 56, Folder PHGEN127)
  - A view of Falcon Lair, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 56, Folder PHGEN128)
  - A view of Rough Point, Doris Duke's Newport, Rhode Island Cottage, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 56, Folder PHGEN129)
  - A view of Shangri La from the Pacific Ocean, undated (reproduction on foam core) (Box 56, Folder PHGEN130)
  - Ambrotype of unknown woman. Photograph is in a decorative case, circa late 1800s (Box 73, Folder PHGEN131)
- Newport Restoration Foundation, 1968-1982
  Photographs in this series primarily document interior and exterior renovations to several NRF homes, and on a lesser scale the inventory of doors and mantels in several homes.
  - Polaroids taken of various NRF houses, 1982 (Box 57, Folder PHNRF001)
  - Color photographs of the moving of Cotton House, an NRF house in Newport. The moving of this house was part of the Queen Anne Square Project. The house belongs to NRF, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder PHNRF002)
  - Black and white and sepia photographs documenting potential real estate purchases by NRF, 1968 (Box 57, Folder PHNRF003)
  - Color photographs of renovations to NRF homes. Includes interior and exterior shots. Each photograph has identification on back, circa 1970s (Box 57, Folder PHNRF004)
  - NRF inventory photographs of doors and mantels, circa 1970s (1 of 2) (Box 57, Folder PHNRF005)
  - NRF inventory photographs of doors and mantels, circa 1970s (1 of 2) (Box 57, Folder PHNRF005)
  - Color photographs of renovations to several NRF homes. Includes interior and exterior shots. Each photographs has identification on back, 1977-1981 (1 of 2) (Box 57, Folder PHNRF006)
  - Color photographs of renovations to several NRF homes. Includes interior and exterior shots. Each photographs has identification on back, 1977-1981 (2 of 2) (Box 57, Folder PHNRF006)
- New York Apartments/New York Mansion, 1914-1997
  This series primarily document the interiors of the New York Mansion and Doris Duke's apartment at 475 Park Avenue in New York City.
  - Selection of color photographs documenting the interior rooms of the New York apartment at 475 Park Avenue, 1997 (Box 17, Folder PHNYA001)
  - Inventory of 6 Haitian paintings moved from Beverly Hills to NY apartment, 1993 (Box 17, Folder PHNYA002)
  - Selection of photos documenting some furnishings at 1 E. 78th St. after donation of house to NYU. Includes some negatives, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder PHNYM001)
  - Black and white photograph of newspaper page from The New York Times revealing the interior of the James B. Duke mansion at 5th and 78th Street, 1914 (Box 17, Folder PHNYM002)
- Rough Point, 1922-2003
  This series includes interior shots of different rooms in Rough Point and exterior views of Rough Point including some of Doris Duke as a child and as an adult. Some of the photographs document home improvements and work progress at Rough Point.
  - Series of color photos of exterior views of Rough Point and surrounding area. Also includes photos of Doris Duke looking out the window at Rough Point and shots of her at beach with dog and friend. Folder includes 2 photos of portraits from inside the house (Doris and Nanaline), 1968 (Box 58, Folder PHRP001)
  - Black and white photographs of Rough Point covered in snow, 1969 (Box 58, Folder PHRP002)
  - Series of color photos removed from one red and white spiral photo album. This selection of images contains photos of Rough Point, 1 interior and 4 exterior shots. In addition, several photos show the town of Newport, Langely-King House, and Doris Duke, 1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP003)
  - Series of color photographs from red and white photo album documenting Miss Duke's investigations of historic homes in Newport. File also includes three interior shots of Rough Point, 1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP004)
  - Doris Duke standing on the lawn next to Rough Point, looking east, toward Middletown and Little Compton on the horizon toward the right. Rocks at the edge of the grass delineate the Cliff Walk, circa 1922 (Box 58, Folder PHRP007)
  - Images of Doris Duke, Johnny Gomez, and Tucker children at Rough Point, 1960-1965 (Box 58, Folder PHRP008)
  - Selection of slides relating to Rough Point, particularly the exterior of the residence, 1960-1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP009)
  - Selection of slides relating to Rough Point. Several slides show shields on stain glass windows, 1960-1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP010)
  - Selection of slides relating to Rough Point, 1960-1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP011)
  - Selection of slides relating to Rough Point, 1960-1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP012)
  - Selection of slides relating to Newport. Some photos taken from plane. Plot of land below could be Rough Point. Folder includes one shot of Johnny Gomez, 1960-1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP013)
  - Selection of slides relating to Rough Point and jazz festival in Newport, 1960-1970 (Box 58, Folder PHRP014)
  - Selection of color photos of exteriors of Rough Point and shots of dogs on the grounds, 1970-1975 (Box 58, Folder PHRP015)
  - Black and white photographs of the ballroom at Rough Point, 1960 (Box 58, Folder PHRP016)
  - Black and white photographs documenting the dog kennels built at Rough Point, circa 1963 (Box 58, Folder PHRP017)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting damage and disarray at Rough Point as a result of two wind storms (Aug and Sept, 1954), 1954 (Box 58, Folder PHRP018)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting home improvements to Rough Point. Letter to David Rimmer from Howard ? provides descriptions of photos, 1963 (Box 58, Folder PHRP019)
  - Black and white photograph of Rough Point, taken from water, circa 1966 (Box 59, Folder PHRP005)
  - Black and white photograph of Rough Point, taken from lawn, undated (Box 59, Folder PHRP006)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting improvements and work progress at Rough Point, 1964 May 6 (Box 60, Folder PHRP020)
  - Polaroids of shields of stained glass. Shields are most likely located in the Main Stair Hall Landing at Rough Point, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder PHRP021)
  - Selection of Black and white photographs documenting building conditions at Rough Point, 1963 (Box 60, Folder PHRP022)
  - Color photos of "coaching week" at Rough Point and images of jewelry exhibit. Images sent to Joan Spero by Phil Mello, 2003 (Box 60, Folder PHRP023)
  - Color photographs of Doris Duke's bedroom, yellow Living Room, and Solarium at Rough Point, circa 2001 (Box 60, Folder PHRP024)
  - Color photographs of the exterior of Rough Point, circa 2001 (Box 60, Folder PHRP025)
  - Color photographs of rooms, contents and a few exterior shots of Rough Point. Includes negatives, 1983 (1 of 2) (Box 60, Folder PHRP026)
  - Color photographs of rooms, contents and a few exterior shots of Rough Point. Includes negatives, 1983 (2 of 2) (Box 60, Folder PHRP026)
  - View of Cliff Walk from Rough Point. Baby and Princess, camels, seen in background, 1988 (Box 60, Folder PHRP027)
  - Color photographs and negatives of Rough Point, Newport, RI. Includes camels, Baby and Princess, and dogs, including Kimo, circa 1980s, 1993 (Box 60, Folder PHRP028)
  - Color images of interior repair work at Rough Point, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 60, Folder PHRP029)
- Southeast Asian Art and Culture (SEAAC), 1960-1972
  This series primarily documents the lifecycle of SEAAC. It includes color photographs of sculptures and places in Thailand, most probably a trip taken as part of research for SEAAC, the interior of the Coach Barn containing the SEAAC exhibit, and black and white photos of possible acquisitions for SEAAC.
  - Color photos documenting trip to Thailand(?). Includes images of sculptures, buildings, etc., circa 1970s (1 of 3) (Box 17, Folder PHSEAAC012)
  - Color photos documenting trip to Thailand(?). Includes images of sculptures, buildings, etc., circa 1970s (2 of 3) (Box 17, Folder PHSEAAC012)
  - Color photos documenting trip to Thailand(?). Includes images of sculptures, buildings, etc., circa 1970s (3 of 3) (Box 17, Folder PHSEAAC012)
  - Color photographs of sculptures and places in Thailand. Most probably, trip taken as part of research for SEAAC, 1960-1965 (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC001)
  - Color photographs of sculptures and places in Thailand. Most probably, trip taken as part of research for SEAAC, 1960-1965 (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC001)
  - Color photographs of the interior of the Coach Barn containing the SEAAC exhibit. Includes transparencies, 1972 (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC005)
  - Black and white photos showing interior of Coach Barn containing SEAAC exhibit by Camera Associates, 1972 (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC006)
  - Black and white photo and contact sheet showing interior of Coach Barn containing SEAAC exhibit by T. Slade, circa 1972 (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC007)
  - Color photos and slides showing the interior of the Coach Barn containing SEAAC objects. Photos by T. Slade, 1972 (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC008)
  - Color photos of detailing on an unidentified building, possibly in Thailand, 1963 (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC009)
  - Black and white photos of possible acquisitions for SEAAC. Photos sent to Nancy Tingley for Foundation by Francois de Berenx, circa 1960s (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC010)
  - Black and white photos of various homes and select temples in Thailand, circa 1960s (Box 61, Folder PHSEAAC011)
  - Black and white photographs of art objects from SEAAC. Many have descriptions on back, undated (Box 62, Folder PHSEAAC013)
  - Black and white photographs of two altars from SEAAC collections, undated (Box 62, Folder PHSEAAC014)
- Shangri La, 1925-1960
  This series documents Doris Duke's life in Hawaii. Images include early construction work of Shangri La, trips that Doris Duke took with her friends prior to the completion of Shangri La, trips around the islands, interior and exterior shots of Shangri La, a professional photo shoot of Doris Duke and her husband James Cromwell, social events including luaus and weddings, and furniture and clothing inventories. Of particular interest are color glass mounted slides of Doris Duke and James Cromwell with basketball team they sponsored in the mid-1930s.